A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.31 (A2005) FA491
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2005.091: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2003; AC.2005.091; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3763.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.091.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 99016 - BUILDING SUPPORT FOR NEW EMPLOYMENT POLICIES AND PRACTICES, 1998 (Box R3763)
    - RF 99016 #31 - ECONOMIC OPPORTUNITY INSTITUTE - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2000-2002 (Box R3763)
    - RF 99016 #32 - INSTITUTE FOR WOMEN'S POLICY RESEARCH - TWO PROJECTS: EDUCATION AND TRAINING TO WOMEN ON WELFARE; UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE REFORM, 2000-2001 (Box R3763)
    - RF 99017 #9 - NATIONAL ECONOMIC AND DEVELOPMENT AND LAW CENTER - TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE FOR COMMUNITY BUILDING ORGANIZATIONS IN CALIFORNIA, 2000 (Box R3763)
    - RF 99019 - BELLAGIO INNOVATION FUND, 1993-1994 (Box R3763)
    - RF 99020 #213 - AFRICA UNIVERSITY (ZIMBABWE) - WORKSHOP FOR SOIL AND PLANT ANALYTICAL LABORATORY TECHNOLOGISTS IN SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1999-2001 (Box R3763)
    - RF 99020 #214 - BRAZILIAN AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH ENTERPRISE - MARGINAL SOILS WORKSHOP PROCEEDINGS, 2000-2001 (Box R3763)
    - RF 99020 #217 - ZIMBABWE - LANDS AND AGRICULTURE (MINISTRY OF) - MICRO-ECONOMICS RESEARCH AND SOIL FERTILITY IN FARMERS' FIELDS, 1999-2003 (Box R3763)
    - RF 99020 #221 - INTERNATIONAL LIVESTOCK RESEARCH INSTITUTE (KENYA) - CROP AND LIVESTOCK PRODUCTION DATABASE, 1996-2001 (Box R3763)
    - RF 99020 #222 - UNIVERSITY OF MISSOURI (COLUMBIA) - INSTITUTIONALIZATION OF KARI'S SOCIO-ECONOMIC DIVISION, 1999-2001 (Box R3763)
    - RF 99020 #225 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - SOIL MANAGEMENT AT KISSII, KITALE, AND KATUMANI, 1997-2002 (Box R3763)
    - RF 99021 - SECOND CONTRACEPTIVE TECHNOLOGY REVOLUTION, 1993-2000 (Box R3763)
    - RF 99021 - SECOND CONTRACEPTIVE TECHNOLOGY REVOLUTION - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-2000 (Box R3763)
- AC.2005.096: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-2004; AC.2005.096; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3765, R3766.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.096.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 99033 #59 - NATIONAL BOARD FOR PROFESSIONAL TEACHING STANDARDS - ACCOMPLISHED TEACHING AND IMPORTANCE OF NATIONAL BOARD CERTIFICATION, 1999-2002 (Box R3765)
    - RF 99035 - E and CO. - TRANSITION TO A NEW ENERGY PARADIGM, 1993-2004 (Box R3765)
    - RF 99035 - E and CO. - TRANSITION TO A NEW ENERGY PARADIGM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-2004 (Box R3765)
    - RF 99036 - STRENGTHENING PUBLIC HEALTH PRACTICE IN ZIMBABWE AND ELSEWHERE, 1991-2000 (Box R3766)
    - RF 99036 - STRENGTHENING PUBLIC HEALTH PRACTICE IN ZIMBABWE AND ELSEWHERE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-2000 (Box R3766)
- AC.2005.098: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1997-2004; AC.2005.098; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3767.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.098.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 99037 - HEALTH EQUITY FRONTIERS, 1999 (Box R3767)
    - RF 99037 #10 - UNIVERSITY OF THE WESTERN CAPE (SOUTH AFRICA) - EQUITY GAUGE INITIATIVE, 2000-2004 (Box R3767)
    - RF 99038 #3 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - MULTILATERAL INITIATIVE ON MALARIA TO STRENGHEN RESEARCH CAPABILITY IN AFRICA, 1997-2002 (Box R3767)
    - RF 99039 - DISEASE SURVEILLANCE, 1999 (Box R3767)
    - RF 99039 #1 - INTERNATIONAL SOCIETY FOR INFECTIOUS DISEASES - PROMED-MAIL'S ACTIVITIES, 1999-2002 (Box R3767)
    - RF 99042 #80 - EASTERN MICHIGAN UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE ON "CHANGING WORLDVIEW OF ISLAMIC PUBLICS", 2000-2002 (Box R3767)
    - RF 99042 #82 - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL HISTORY FOUNDATION OF TURKEY - LOCAL HISTORY AND MUSEOLOGY PROJECT, 1998-2002 (Box R3767)
    - RF 99042 #84 - JERUSALEM INTERNATIONAL BOOK FAIR (ISRAEL) - 20TH JERUSALEM INTERNATIONAL BOOK FAIR, 1999-2001 (Box R3767)
    - RF 99042 #86 - UNIVERSITY OF OKLAHOMA - CONFERENCE ON STATUS OF JERUSALEM, 1999-2001 (Box R3767)
    - RF 99043 - ROLE OF RELIGION IN CIVIL SOCIETY, 1995-2000 (Box R3767)
    - RF 99043 #18 - MINNEAPOLIS INSTITUTE OF ARTS - ARTS AND RELIGION IN THE TWIN CITIES CONSORTIUM, 1999-2002 (Box R3767)
    - RF 99044 #628 - LA MORADA CORPORATION FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF WOMEN (CHILE) - CONFERENCE ON WOMEN'S MEMORY AND HISTORY, 2000-2003 (Box R3767)
- AC.2005.100: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1995-2005; AC.2005.100; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3768.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.100.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 99055 #173 - FORUM FOR AFRICAN WOMEN EDUCATIONALISTS, GHANA CHAPTER - GIRLS' SEXUAL MATURATION AND MENSTRUAL PRACTICES IN SCHOOLS, 2000-2001 (Box R3768)
    - RF 99055 #174 - MATERI GIRLS' CENTRE (KENYA) - HEALTH TRAINING PROGRAM IN THARAKA, 1999-2002 (Box R3768)
    - RF 99055 #178 - (FEMALE PARTICIPATION IN AFRICAN EDUCATION) - MULTILINGUALISM IN DEVELOPMENT OF CURRICULA FOR GIRLS, 2000-2001 (Box R3768)
    - RF 99055 #180 - NNABAGEREKA DEVELOPMENT TRUST FUND (UGANDA) - CHILDREN'S WELFARE AND ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT, 2000-2002 (Box R3768)
    - RF 99055 #181 - WORLD BANK - STRATEGIC RESOURCE PLANNING FOR GIRLS' EDUCATION IN AFRICA, 1995-2005 (Box R3768)
    - RF 99055 #182 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - MEETING TO ADVANCE GIRLS' MATHEMATICS AND SCIENCE EDUCATION, 2000-2001 (Box R3768)
    - RF 99055 #185 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - GIRLS' ACCESS TO AND PARTICIPATION IN EDUCATION, 2000-2003 (Box R3768)
    - RF 99055 #186 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY - GIRLS' ACCESSS TO AND PARTICIPATION IN EDUCATION, 2000-2002 (Box R3768)
    - RF 99055 #187 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - GIRLS' ACCESS TO AND PARTICIPATION IN EDUCATION, 2000-2002 (Box R3768)
    - RF 99055 #193 - INSTITUTE FOR REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH TRAINING AND RESEARCH (KENYA) - PRE-ADOLESCENTS AND THE PROCESS OF SEXUAL MATURATION, 2000-2002 (Box R3768)